Caleb Park (Legal name: Jee Hyun Park) 89 Rossmore Court, Park Road

(+44) 07455 641 392 cpark@london.edu http://cpark.me

## Summary

London, UK NW1 6XZ

I am a mathematician with a PhD in Operations Management, expected 2022.

My research centers around data-driven decisions under uncertainty, such as experimental design and auction design. I mainly use product-level data to give insights to store-level decisions. My PhD research has been implemented to a global retail network for in-store field experiments.

I have three years of industry experience with data-intensive research from South Korea, and five years of MBA-level teaching experience during my PhD. I am a Korean living abroad since the age of four.

### Education

## London Business School

London, UK

Ph.D., Management Science and Operations

2016 - Aug. 2022 (expected)

- Dissertation: Data-driven decisions in experimental design and combinatorial auctions
- Advisors: Jérémie Gallien and Gah-Yi Ban

# Judge Business School, University of Cambridge

Cambridge, UK

M.Phil. Management Science and Operations (Distinction) 73/100

2012 - 2013

- Dissertation: Competitive dynamic pricing with alternating offers

## Trinity College, University of Cambridge

B.A.(Hons.) Mathematics (2:1) 68/100

Cambridge, UK 2009 - 2012

Seoul. South Korea

## Work Experience

## CalebABC, Co., Ltd.

Data Scientist Mar 2015 - Aug. 2016

- Healthcare data management software for public and private hospitals
- Project manager of B-Box, statistics and analytics tool for healthcare
- Algorithm design for diagnosis-related groups (DRG) costing software

### Security Management Institute

Seoul, South Korea

Researcher, promoted to Senior Researcher

Jul 2013 - Feb 2015

- Center for Program Analysis and Evaluation
- Government projects in national security, with focus on analytics and costing

#### Research in Management Science

#### Design and evaluation of field experiments in retail store networks

- with Prof. Jérémie Gallien (LBS) and Prof. Adam J. Mersereau (UNC Chapel-Hill)
  - Novel method to evaluate experimental designs according to performances on data-driven simulations
  - Implemented the algorithm to a global fashion retail network through practice-based research
  - to be submitted to Management Science

### Structural estimation of combinatorial auctions

- with Prof. Gah-Yi Ban (Maryland) and Prof. Richard Steinberg (LSE)
  - Used a novel stochastic approximation algorithm to solve first price sealed-bid combinatorial auctions with the NP-hard "winner determination" problem
  - to be submitted to Management Science

#### Other Research and Publications

The Republic of Korea's coronavirus pandemic response and health system preparedness. (with Hoon Sang Lee, Sangjune Kim and Inseok Lee) Asia Development Bank (ADB) Report, Sept 2021.

Quantitative Methods for Health Care Management. (Korean Edition) Wiley & Sons, 2016. Translation and adaptation work under CalebABC Co., Ltd.

## Teaching Experience

#### London Business School

London, UK

Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2021

- Teaching Assistant
  - Data science and operations management courses for MBA and Executive Education programmes
  - Data courses: Decision and risk analysis, Data analytics for managers, Data analytics for finance,
    Introduction to Python, Applied programming in R, Introduction to R for data science
  - Operations courses: Supply chain management, Value chain management, Project management

#### University College London, UCL School of Management

London, UK

Teaching Assistant and Seminar Leader

Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2021

- Undergraduate: Business intelligence, Decision science, Decision and risk analysis
- Postgraduate: Statistics for business research, Decision and risk analysis

#### Awards

Practice-based research, Zara SA (€150,000)

2018

PhD Programme Scholarship with Tuition Waiver, London Business School

2016-2021

#### Other interests

Fantasy football, Tennis, Badminton, Music theory, Turkish